(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-20T18:15:11.595968",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
ヴァイスシュヴァルツ！
Weiß Schwarz!
ホロライブプロダクションがまたまたカードに大集合！
Hololive Production gathers once again in cards!
広がるヴァイスシュヴァルツ！
Expanding Weiß Schwarz!
ブースターパック ホロライブプロダクション Vol.2 3月24日(金)発売
Booster Pack Hololive Production Vol.2 releasing March 24th!
Vol.2
Vol. 2
ブシロード
Bushiroad
パッと来い 雷の音で バイバイ 巡る旅へ
Come on! With the sound of thunder, bye-bye, on a wandering journey.
だけど世界がなんちゃって もうやめにして
But the world is just pretending, so let's quit that already.
どうしちゃったの絶対絶対絶対 好きでしょ
What's wrong with you? You definitely, definitely, definitely love it, right?
愛ゆえにバイバイ もうラッシュインサマー
Out of love, bye-bye, rushing into summer now!
hololive SUPER EXPO 2023 デジタルメッセージボード
hololive SUPER EXPO 2023 Digital Message Board
グッズ ラインナップ
Goods Lineup
商品ラインナップ！
Product Lineup!
ホロスターズ
HOLOSTARS
hololive production Art Collection
ホロライブ 事務所グッズ
Hololive Office Goods
HOLOLIVE ALTERNATIVE グッズ
HOLOLIVE ALTERNATIVE Goods
マンガート ビームス コラボグッズ
MANGART BEAMS Collaboration Goods
holo*27 コラボグッズ
holo*27 Collaboration Goods
BUSHIROAD グッズ
BUSHIROAD Goods
GOOD SMILE COMPANY グッズ
GOOD SMILE COMPANY Goods
OFFICIAL ITEMS
PENLIGHT COLORS
ヴァイスシュヴァルツ！
Weiß Schwarz!
ホロライブプロダクションが またまたカードに大集合！
Hololive Production is gathering in cards once again!
広がるヴァイスシュヴァルツ！
Expanding Weiß Schwarz!
ホロライブプロダクション Vol.2
hololive production Vol.2
ブシロード
Bushiroad
愛とか恋とか全部くだらない
Love and crushes are all meaningless,
がっつきするだけ ダメを知るだけ
I just get disappointed, I just see the bad.
あたし馬鹿ね ダサい逆走じゃん
I'm just stupid, running the wrong way.
だって前回ヤンチャって もうやめてしたい
Because I want to quit being reckless like last time.
どうしちゃったの 絶好調 絶対絶対好きでしょ
What's wrong? You're in top form, you definitely like me!
Are you embarrassed?　今悩んでる somehow
Are you embarrassed? Right now we're rushing somehow.
見上げた夜空 希望はあるかな
Looking up at the night sky, is there hope?
釣って一杯々々で 零れてるかな
Tracing it step by step, am I spilling over?
ひとりきりだった 寂しかったんだね
I was all alone, I was so lonely.
どうして鳴り止まないことは こんな近くじゃないか
Why won't the music stop right so close by?
Parade, Parade, Parade！ 輝くんだよ
Parade, Parade, Parade! It's time to shine,
呼び合う声を 合図に
with the voices calling out as our signal.
探しにいくよ スタートは何度だって
We'll go search, the start is however many times.
ただ独り言を紡いだ
I just wove my monologue,
ただ始まりたくて走った
I just ran because I wanted to begin.
遠く 暗がり灯った
Far away, lighting up the darkness.
hololive SUPER EXPO 2023 デジタルメッセージボード
[hololive SUPER EXPO 2023 Digital Message Board]
hololive SUPER EXPO 2023 グッズラインナップ紹介
[hololive SUPER EXPO 2023 Merchandise Lineup]
繋いだ真っ赤な糸が愛おしくてよしよししちゃう
The connected bright red thread is so dear, I just want to pet you.
どこにも行かないように縛って ほらあなただけに寄り添っていい子にできてたのに
Tie you up so you can't go anywhere, clinging only to you even though I was a good girl.
どうしちゃったの 絶対絶対絶対好きでしょ
What's wrong? You definitely, definitely, definitely love me, right?
どうしちゃったの いっぱいっぱいっぱい愛して
What's wrong? Love me loads and loads and loads!
大嫌いな自分に「じゃあね」って言って
Saying "see ya" to the me I hate so much,
バイバイバイ やっほー
bye-bye-bye, hoo-ray!
変われちゃう？ きっと変われちゃう？
Can I change? Surely I can change?
ねえ 美味じゃない？ ごっこ遊びじゃない
Isn't it wonderful? This isn't pretend play.
up all night キャーキャーして
Up all night, giggling away,
まあまあいいじゃん
hey, that's pretty good!
失敗して おっおっおっ 危ないかも
Making mistakes, oh-oh-oh, might be in trouble,
負けたくないから 燃えてきちゃうんだ
but I don't want to lose, so I'm getting fired up!
スイッチひとつで びびるほど全開
With just one switch, running at full throttle,
いくぜ 追いかけ追い越せ で 未来へ 転がりながら走っていくんだ
let's go, chasing, overtaking, rolling into the future!
心痛いけどね… 中途半端はしたくない
My heart aches, but... I don't want to do things halfway,
だって 全然 やんないちゃって
because quitting right when things get going
もうやめにしたいときも
is something I never want to do!
勝ちたい理由と 負けない理由で
With reasons to win and reasons not to lose,
ずっとずっと ここにいるよ
I'll always, always be right here!
大嫌いな自分に「じゃあね」って言って
Saying "see ya" to the me I hate so much,
バイバイバイ やっほー
bye-bye-bye, hoo-ray!
変われちゃう？ きっと変われちゃう？
Can I change? Surely I can change?
ねえ 美味じゃない？ ごっこ遊びじゃない
Isn't it wonderful? This isn't pretend play.
絶対 好きな僕見つけようぜ
Let's definitely find the me we love!
up and down バタバタして つらいときも
Up and down, even when things are frantic and tough,
止まってなんかいられないでしょ やるしかない
we can't just stop, we've got no choice but to do it!
悲しい気持ちに 気づかれないように 思ってることは 閉じ込めたままで
Hiding sadness so no one notices, keeping feelings locked inside,
強がりをバフして ウェルカム状態
buffing our bravado and welcoming the state of mind
勝てない気しかしないじゃん おっけー？
where we feel like we can't win... right?
言い訳なんての… 満点ダンスしたいじゃない？
No excuses... don't we want to dance a 100-point routine?
待って 限界 やんなったって もう無理って言えないよ
Wait, even if we reach our limit, we can't say we're done!
勝ちたい理由が 負けない理由が ずっとずっと ここにあるよ
Reasons to win and reasons not to lose are always right here!
大嫌いな自分に「じゃあね」って言って
Saying "see ya" to the me I hate so much,
バイバイバイ やっほー
bye-bye-bye, hoo-ray!
越えれちゃう？ きっと越えれちゃう？
Can I overcome it? Surely I can overcome it?
ねえ 決まりじゃない？ ごっこ遊びじゃない
Isn't it a rule? This isn't pretend play.
変われちゃう？ きっと変われちゃう？
Can I change? Surely I can change?
ねえ 美味じゃない？ ごっこ遊びじゃない
Isn't it wonderful? This isn't pretend play.
絶対 好きな僕見つけようぜ
Let's definitely find the me we love!
だって 全然 やんないちゃって もうやめにしたいときも
Even when we want to stop and quit completely,
勝ちたい理由と 負けない理由で ずっとずっと ここにいるよ
with reasons to win and not to lose, we'll always be here!
大嫌いな自分に「じゃあね」って言って
Saying "see ya" to the me I hate so much,
バイバイバイ やっほー
bye-bye-bye, hoo-ray!
変われちゃう？ きっと変われちゃう？
Can I change? Surely I can change?
ねえ 美味じゃない？ ごっこ遊びじゃない
Isn't it wonderful? This isn't pretend play.
待って 限界 やんなったって もう無理って言えないよ
Wait, even if we reach our limit, we can't say we're done!
勝ちたい理由が 負けない理由が ずっとずっと ここにあるよ
Reasons to win and reasons not to lose are always right here!
大嫌いな自分に「じゃあね」って言って
Saying "see ya" to the me I hate so much,
バイバイバイ やっほー
bye-bye-bye, hoo-ray!
越えれちゃう？ きっと越えれちゃう？
Can I overcome it? Surely I can overcome it?
ねえ 決まりじゃない？ ごっこ遊びじゃない
Isn't it a rule? This isn't pretend play.
変われちゃう？ きっと変われちゃう？
Can I change? Surely I can change?
ねえ 美味じゃない？ ごっこ遊びじゃない
Isn't it wonderful? This isn't pretend play.
絶対 好きな僕見つけようぜ
Let's definitely find the me we love!
だって前回やんなっちゃっても辞めていたい時も
Even when I'm sick of it all and want to quit,
勝ちたい理由と負けない理由で
driven by reasons to win and not to lose,
ずっとずっとここにいるよ
I'll always, always be right here.
大嫌いな自分にじゃねって言ってバイバイバイ
Say bye-bye to the self I hate so much!
壊れちゃっていいの？壊れちゃっていいの？
Is it okay to break? Is it okay to break?
現実なんかだってもう無理って言えないよ
I can't keep saying reality is too much to bear!
勝ちたい理由と負けない理由がずっとずっとここにあるよ
Reasons to win and not to lose are always, always right here.
大嫌いな自分にじゃねって言ってバイバイバイ
Say bye-bye to the self I hate so much!
壊れちゃっていいの？壊れちゃっていいの？
Is it okay to break? Is it okay to break?
意地張ってんじゃない？ずっと遊びじゃない！壊れちゃっていいの？
Aren't you being stubborn? This isn't just playing! Is it okay to break?
絶対好きな僕見つけようぜ
Let's find the me we're bound to love!
あたしヴァンパイア　いいの？吸っちゃっていいの？
I'm a vampire. Is it okay? Is it okay if I bite you?
「もう無理もう無理」なんて悪い子だね
Saying "I can't take it anymore" makes me a bad girl, huh?
試したいの　いっぱいではき出したいの
I want to try it out, I want to vent it all out.
まだ絶対いけるよ
I can still definitely go on!
最低最高　ずっと行き来してる
Lowest and highest, going back and forth forever.
甘くなる不安の果実　No more 発展
The sweet fruit of anxiety, no more progression.
嫉妬息をしてても　要らないだけうるさいだけ
Even when breathing jealousy, it's just unneeded, just noisy.
誰かといれば　それはそれで
If I'm with someone, that in itself
乱れてく気持ちの帳尻合わない
messes up the balance of my feelings.
狂れていてもう感じてるへえ
Even when going crazy, I can still feel it, huh?
出逢い系確かめたら知れるかも秘密の
If I check a dating app, I might learn a secret.
秘密も　切ないも　君のすべてを喰らうまで説教
My secrets, my sorrow, until I devour all of you—a lecture!
あたしヴァンパイア　いいの？吸っちゃっていいの？
I'm a vampire. Is it okay? Is it okay if I bite you?
「もう無理もう無理」なんて
Saying "I can't take it anymore"
試したいの　いっぱいではき出したいの　まだ絶対いけるよ
I want to try it out, I want to vent it all out, I can still definitely go on!
求め合ってから絡まってほらよ　感じないては捨てたら
Craving each other, tangling up, hey, if you throw away numbness,
初めは捨て　愛嬌をください
first throw it away, please show some affection!
まだ絶対いけるよ
I can still definitely go on!
あたしヴァンパイア　まずはこっち向いて
I'm a vampire, first look this way!
最初の重い洗いざらい
Washing away the initial heavy feelings completely,
吐き出したならまさにばかり
if I vomited them out, it's just like that.
懲り切れないけどあまっりじゃない
I never learn, but isn't it too much?
ちょっと頭で考えてもう
Thinking about it a bit in my head,
繰り返しじゃないこのままじゃまだ
isn't it repeating? Staying like this,
求めてまたチャンスを逃すのが
craving and missing the chance again
破れかけた気持ちの帳尻合わせたいけど叶えたいけど
I want to balance my torn feelings, but I want to make it come true.
秘密も　切ないも　君のすべてを喰らうまで説教
My secrets, my sorrow, until I devour all of you—a lecture!
楽しいか　悲しいか
Is it fun? Is it sad?
溺れるまで学習になれるね絶叫
Drowning until I get used to it—screaming!
あたしヴァンパイア　いいの？吸っちゃっていいの？
I'm a vampire. Is it okay? Is it okay if I bite you?
「もう無理もう無理」なんて
Saying "I can't take it anymore"
試したいの　いっぱいではき出したいの　まだ絶対いけるよ
I want to try it out, I want to vent it all out, I can still definitely go on!
死に物狂いよ　気も狂っちゃっていいの
Fighting for my life, is it okay to go crazy too?
溺れ溺れダンス踊って欲しい見えないは
Drowning, drowning, dancing, wanting you to hold me tight, invisible,
絶対いけないほら絶対さきよ
definitely shouldn't go, hey, absolutely ahead!
求め合ってから絡まってほら何回ね
Craving each other, tangling up, hey, how many times?
確かに見えるような穴の中で
Inside a hole where it clearly looks visible,
絶叫して愛をください　まだ絶対いけるよ
screaming, please give me love, I can still definitely go on!
あたしヴァンパイア　まずはこっち向いて
I'm a vampire, first look this way!
んんなあああああ
Nnnnaaaaa!
ちょっと楽しみに待っててねのおつわわわ！
Wait excitedly for me, tsu wawawa!
あんなああああ　みんないいよお
Annaaaaa, everyone, it's good!
ドラマティックに信じて　全力とって下に持ち上げて飛ばれよ！
Believe dramatically, take your all, lift it down and let it fly!
こいつもあいつもどいつもこいつもだないかっこばかりするだけでめおしろだけ
This guy, that guy, everyone's just looking cool and only thinking about themselves.
あたしぼこれださい局そうじゃん　困るところは新たに文字だしまい失敗するのにびみってるだけ　覚悟なしのきびしめの条件じゃん
My clumsy self is so pathetic, right? When troubled, I show new characters, failing while hesitating, harsh conditions without resolve, right?
こんな時どんな数えればいいか教えてほしいの！
Tell me what kind of numbers I should count at a time like this!
あいつけどだとかそんな言葉で壊れてるさいね
Breaking apart with words like "that guy" or whatever, right?
宣誓しちゃいます!うちらトップ目指して走ります!
We hereby declare! We're running to the very top!
人気出ちゃいます!?すぐにネットチケット高騰
Are we getting popular!? Net tickets skyrocketing right away!
急成長
Rapid growth!
アイドルその一
Idol rule one:
笑顔全開
Big smiles!
アイドルその二
Idol rule two:
ファンを大事に
Cherish the fans!
アイドルその三
Idol rule three:
汗は勲章
Sweat is a badge of honor!
愛されよう!
Be loved!
朝練で足がガクガクです
Morning practice has my legs all shaky!
眠気まなこ猫の手借りたい
Sleepy-eyed, I want to borrow a cat's paw!
毎日超ハード…
"Every day is super hard..."
向いてないってアンチの言葉に泣きたくなる日も
Days when anti comments make me want to cry,
周りのみんない置いてかれる日も
and days when everyone around me leaves me behind...
喰いしばってしがみつきたい
I want to bite down and hold on tight!
しんどい時でも頑張ってって言ってくれたから
Because you told me to do my best even when times are tough,
全身全霊声が届くまで歌ってみせるよ!
I'll sing with my body and soul until my voice reaches you!
君からのエール!コール!
Your cheers and calls!
マジで頑張れちゃいます!
I can really do my best!
限界突破ー!
Breakthrough!
満員御礼!やばい!?どこも入場規制中!
House packed! Oh no!? Admission restricted everywhere!
大成功!?
Big success!?
アイドルその四
Idol rule four:
背筋はぴんと
Posture straight and tall!
アイドルその五
Idol rule five:
前髪キープ
Keep the bangs in place!
アイドルその六
Idol rule six:
間食はダメ!
No snacking!
可愛くね
Stay cute!
赤点連発イノコリかあ?
Failing grades over and over, detention?
そこ私の席なんですけど…
But that's my seat...
占い最下位だー…
Dead last in fortune-telling...
大凶!?
Terrible luck!?
しんどい時でも頑張ってって言ってくれたから
Because you told me to do my best even when times are tough,
全身全霊声が届くまで歌ってみせるよ!
I'll sing with my body and soul until my voice reaches you!
君の一番は誰?言わなくてもわかるよね?
Who is your number one? You know without me saying it, right?
聞かせて
Let me hear it!
推し変厳禁!絶対!私だけしか見ちゃダメっ!
Changing your oshi is strictly forbidden! Absolute! You can only look at me!
宣誓しちゃいます!うちらトップ目指して走ります!
We hereby declare! We're running to the very top!
人気出ちゃいます!?すぐにネットチケット高騰
Are we getting popular!? Net tickets skyrocketing right away!
ちょっと強がりになって出直すわわわわわ
Acting a little tough, I'll fix it wa-wa-wa-wa!
ひとりじゃなんでもない言いたいこと
All by myself, there's nothing I couldn't say...
言えたことないやね
Things I've never been able to say!
止め止め止められないの
Stop, stop, I can't stop it!
悲しくたってまた自己嫌悪ね
Even when I'm sad, self-loathing hits again.
待てよ待ておんなのあたし
Wait, wait, me, a girl—
困っちゃっていいやいや
It's annoying, oh well!
可愛いないのこの孤独感
This loneliness is so uncute.
困っちゃっていいやいや
It's annoying, oh well!
骨が鳴ってハイになって私まだ耐え切れないよ
Bones creaking, getting high, I still can't endure it yet!
待って香水
Wait, perfume—
飛び込んでみたいから
because I want to dive right in!
待てよ待ておんなのあたし
Wait, wait, me, a girl—
困っちゃっていいやいや
It's annoying, oh well!
剥がれ落ちたメイク すっぴんのアニマル
Makeup peeling away, a barefaced animal.
醜くてもやっちゃうのよ
Even if I'm ugly, I just gotta do it!
おすわりとかできない だって待てでもできない
Can't sit, can't even stay when told to wait.
喉鳴らして いっちゃうまで
Purring in my throat, until I go all the way!
ぶっ飛ばそうぜ 高まるビート
Let's blow it away, the rising beat!
良いも悪いも関係ない
Good or bad doesn't matter at all!
ハマってみようぜ 突破するゲート
Let's get hooked, breaking through the gate!
愛に期待は禁物だよ
Expecting love is forbidden!
ねぇ 止まれないほどに狂いたい
Hey, I want to go crazy enough that I can't stop.
心真っ赤にしてどうしちゃったのよ
Turning my heart bright red, what has happened to me?
痛みすらも愛せたら
If I could love even the pain,
あたしは幸せです
I would be happy.
剥がれ落ちたメイク すっぴんのアニマル
Makeup peeling away, a barefaced animal.
醜くてもやっちゃうのよ
Even if I'm ugly, I just gotta do it!
あがっちゃってよ くるっちゃってよ めぐっちゃってよ ンアッハッハ
Rise up, go crazy, go around, n' ahahaha!
いやいや噛み占い甲斐なくてつまらない
No way, fortune-telling bite is unrewarding and boring.
せめてちょっと拒んでほしかったな
At least I wanted you to resist just a little.
少しだけ欲張りるならあたしは幸せになりたいです
If I can be a little greedy, I want to be happy.
剥がれ落ちたメイク すっぴんのアニマル
Makeup peeling away, a barefaced animal.
醜くてもやっちゃうのよ
Even if I'm ugly, I just gotta do it!
おすわりとかできない だって待てでもできない
Can't sit, can't even stay when told to wait.
喉鳴らして いっちゃうまで
Purring in my throat, until I go all the way!
塗り重ねたメイク ばっちりなアニマル
Layered makeup, a picture-perfect animal.
目を開いて待ってるのよ
Waiting with my eyes wide open.
おすわりとかできない だって待てでもできない
Can't sit, can't even stay when told to wait.
喉鳴らして いっちゃうまで
Purring in my throat, until I go all the way!
牙を出し叫べ ざっくゅーんだ
Baring my fangs and shouting, "Zakkuyun!"
あたしは噛み付いたら離さないにゃ
Once I bite down, I won't let go, nya!
剥がれ落ちたメイク すっぴんのアニマル
Makeup peeling away, a barefaced animal.
醜くてもやっちゃうのよ
Even if I'm ugly, I just gotta do it!
あわてんぼうせよ ふうふっちゃってよ めぐっちゃってよ ナハハハ
Hurrying souls, puffing up, swirling around, nahahaha!
唯我独尊でつまんない せめてちょっと困らせて欲しかったな
Self-righteous and boring, at least I wanted you to be troubled a bit.
少しだけ特別れるならあたしは幸せになりたいで
If I can be a bit special, I want to be happy...
ーーす!
--!
剥がれ落ちたメイク すっぴんのアニマル
Makeup peeling away, a barefaced animal.
醜くてもやっちゃうのよ
Even if I'm ugly, I just gotta do it!
おすわりとかできない だって待てでもできない
Can't sit, can't even stay when told to wait.
喉鳴らして いっちゃうまで
Purring in my throat, until I go all the way!
塗り重ねたメイク ばっちりなアニマル
Layered makeup, a picture-perfect animal.
目を開いて待ってるのよ
Waiting with my eyes wide open.
おすわりとかできない だって待てでもできない
Can't sit, can't even stay when told to wait.
喉鳴らして いっちゃうまで
Purring in my throat, until I go all the way!
牙を出し叫べ ざっくゅーんだ
Baring my fangs and shouting, "Zakkuyun!"
あたしは噛み付いたら離さないにゃ
Once I bite down, I won't let go, nya!
塗り重ねたメイク ばっちりなアニマル
Layered makeup, a picture-perfect animal.
目を開いて待ってるのよ
Waiting with my eyes wide open.
にゃおうにゃお にゃおにゃお...
Meow, meow, meow, meow...
ワーイ!
Yay!
ということで息吸ってますけども
And so, we were just catching our breath...
皆さん、こんばみおー！
Everyone, Konbamio!
イエーイ！
Yay!
ホロライブどき生! ハラキリすんな!
Hololive live broadcast! Don't panic!
頭真っ白白読みだよ!
My mind went completely blank!
そして!
And then...
うちうち！うちだよ！
Us, us, it's us!
狼みおだよ！
I'm Ookami Mio!
イエーイ！
Yay!
ちょっと何かやしていいか戸惑うやつそれ
We were wondering what to do next!
もうそれはさておき!二人合わせて!
Well, anyway! Together, the two of us...
おおかみよーすです！
are Ookamiyousu!
イエーイ！
Yay!
戻りましたね
We're back!
戻りました
We're back.
ホロライブフェスアワーブレイクパレードDay2
Hololive Fes Our Bright Parade Day 2
ホロニーノステージいよいよ始まったよー！
Holonyano Stage is finally starting!
イエーイ！
Yay!
いやー本当 声いっぱいありがとー、幕張ー！
Man, thank you so much for all your cheers, Makuhari!
ありがとー！
Thank you!
そしてさ、これ、みんなも見てるよね？ネット配信！
And everyone at home is watching too, right? The online stream!
配信エーイ！ありがとう！
Streaming, yay! Thank you!
ありがとー！
Thank you!
イエーイ、みんなめっちゃ帰ってくれてる！
Yay, everyone came back so much!
元気だなって言われました
They told us we looked energetic!
元気かも
Maybe we are energetic.
元気だ、イエーイ！
We're energetic, yay!
あ、あのさっきさ、おかすかみ先輩の後ろらしいじゃないですか
Ah, earlier, it seems that was behind Okasukami-senpai...
うち、あの、こうやって大きな舞台で、みんながこうやって声、わーって出してくれるの初めてだから
For us, being on such a big stage where everyone raises their voices like that for the first time...
ちょっとどうしていいかわかんなくて、どうすればいいんだろう
We didn't know what to do, wondering what we should do.
なるほど、そうなんですね
I see, is that so?
俺の中か余裕そうも
In my case, I looked composed too.
あ、実は、こより、昨日も1回やってるんですよ、ね？え？
Ah, actually, Koyori did it once yesterday too, right? Eh?
そ、そうなんですか？
Is that so?
そう、そうなんですよ
Yeah, that's right.
え、じゃあ、なんかこう、こう、みんなに投げかける言葉とか、教えてほしいんですけど
Eh, then, I want you to teach me some words to throw out to everyone...
こより先輩！
Koyori-senpai!
あ、いいよ、いいよ、見おく。それはコールアンドレスポンスっていうやつだね！
Ah, sure, sure, Miyoku. That's called a call and response!
コールアンドレスポンスとは一体！
What on earth is a call and response?!
説明しよう！
Let me explain!
コールアンドレスポンスとは、こっちがこうやってなんかバーって投げかけたら、みんながうわーってレスポンスしてくれるという言葉の投げかけ合いなのだよ！
Call and response is when we throw something out like that, and everyone responds, throwing words back and forth!
なるほど！やってみたいっす、やってみたいっす！
I see! I want to try it, I want to try it!
じゃあ、ちょっとやってみますか
Well then, shall we try it?
あの、我々ね、アニマル歌わさせていただきましたけれど
Uh, we sang "Animal", but...
アニマルって、あの、かっこいいのと、かわいいのと、結構ギャップをね、頑張ってやらせていただいたんですよね
For "Animal", we really worked hard on the gap between cool and cute.
すごいギャップある、ね、ギャップある！
There's a huge gap, right, a huge gap!
電源突破！
Power breakthrough!
あ、電源突破。さっきの4文字5文字でね。
Ah, power breakthrough. With those 4 and 5 characters earlier.
電源突破したんですけど。
We broke through the power.
あのね、みんなに、かわいいと思ったか、かっこいいと思ったかって聞いてみます。
So, I want to ask everyone if they thought it was cute or cool.
あ、いいですね、先輩、それ！
Ah, that's great, senpai!
よし、やってみよう、みおくん。
Alright, let's try it, Mio-kun.
じゃあ、おてほんを見せるね。
Well then, I'll show you an example.
まずコおねがいします！じゃあ、アニマルかわいいと思った人ー！
First, please! So, everyone who thought "Animal" was cute!
いっぱいだ、ありがとう！じゃあ、やってみろ、みおくん。
So many, thank you! Now, you try it, Mio-kun.
あれ？でも、こんなにかわいいて言う人がいたら、もしかしたら、かっこいいって言ってくれる人がいなくて、コールアンドレスポンスが成り立たない可能性あるよね？
Huh? But if everyone says it's cute, what if there's no one who says it's cool, and the call and response doesn't work?
あ、確かに、ちょっと寂しい感じになるかもしれないけど、それも修行のうちだ、やってみな、みおくん！
Ah, true, it might feel a bit lonely, but that's part of the training too, give it a try, Mio-kun!
頑張ります！
I'll do my best!
アニマル、かっこいいと思った人ー！
Everyone who thought "Animal" was cool!
あれ？なんか、同じぐらいの圧が。確かに、きた？あれ？ということは、アニマルはかわいくて、かっこいいということなんじゃないでしょうか。
Huh? The pressure was about the same. It really came? Huh? That means "Animal" is both cute and cool, doesn't it?
じゃあ、かっこいいとかわいいと思った人って聞いたら、すごいことになっちゃいますかね？
So if we ask who thought it was both cool and cute, would it be amazing?
もしかしたら、針ーめせが破裂してしまうかもしれない。
If so, Harimese might burst.
じゃあ聞いてみますか。
Then shall we ask?
せーの！アニマルかっこいいと思った人ー！
Ready, go! Everyone who thought "Animal" was cool!
これがコールアンドレスポンスだよ、みおくん。よりいっそうめちゃくちゃ提供になりました！
That's call and response, Mio-kun. It became an even better offering!
じゃあもっとやってみようって言いたいところなんだけど、実は時間というものがあってだね、みおくん。
Now I'd love to say let's do more, but actually there's this thing called time, Mio-kun.
もしかして、もうおしまいなんですか？我々は、おしまいしないといけないんだ。
Could it be that it's already over? We have to finish it.
えーでもね、このライブはまだまだ続いていきますので
Eh, but you know, this live is going to continue even more, so
続いちゃうぞー！ハッシュタグホロニーノをつけて、ぜひぜひスクショとかもいっぱい撮って、呟いてください！
It's gonna continue! Please use the hashtag #HoloNyano, take lots of screenshots, and tweet about them!
はりきって、もう取りました！はい！
We're all fired up and ready! Yes!
いきますよ！
Here we go!
せーの！広がるホロライブ！
Ready, go! Expanding Hololive!
落ち込み携帯どうしたって聞けば 何もないよって言うんだ
When I ask why you're down on your phone, you say it's nothing.
そうかそうか気のせいか でそれで済むものか本当に
"Is that so?" "Just my imagination?" Can we really let it go at that?
心配性の追撃 やりすぎはダメって習った
The relentless barrage of worry, I learned overdoing it is no good.
平気平気ありがとね ってやっぱ普通じゃない
"I'm fine, thanks," but isn't that abnormal after all?
甘え また また また また 全然強がんじゃん
Spoiling me, again, again, again, again. You're acting so tough.
私に任せてね
Leave it to me!
全部言っちゃえばだって なんか苦しそうじゃん
If you just tell me everything, 'cause you look kind of in pain.
言っちゃえばだって それで済むんだね了解
If you just say it, it's all resolved!
笑えるようになるまで 隣にステイでずっとバカな冗談
Staying by your side until you can smile, telling silly jokes all along.
坂道過ごして ずっと ぜんぜん beep beep beep
Spending time on the slope, constantly beep beep beep...
ぜんぜん beep beep beep
Constantly beep beep beep...
落ち込み携帯 気にしちゃって負けた 君が倒れちゃったらやだ
Worried about your phone, I lost. I'd hate for you to collapse.
だってだって不安じゃない これはお手上げかな
Because I'm worried, aren't I? Is this a total surrender?
一体何が贅沢なんだ 誰のためのだろう
What on earth is so luxurious? Who is this for?
こうやって元気付けたり ブレーキ踏んだり
Cheering you up like this, or putting on the brakes.
もう 馬鹿 馬鹿 永遠 自己嫌悪
Oh, foolish, foolish, eternal self-hatred.
好きだ 初めから
I've liked you from the start.
全部言っちゃえばだって なんか苦しそうじゃん
If you just tell me everything, 'cause you look kind of in pain.
言っちゃえばだって それで済むんだね了解
If you just say it, it's all resolved!
君が首突っ込むんだのくらんしそうだな
You sticking your neck into this makes me dizzy.
好きだなんて絶対言えないよ
I could never say I like you.
かんぜん beep beep beep
Completely beep beep beep...
ぜんぜん beep beep beep
Constantly beep beep beep...
君も同じになりなさい 顔を縦に振らせ
You should become the same, make your head nod up and down.
染まれ一切合切 その思いに
Be completely dyed in those feelings.
やっぱり元気でほしいじゃん たといて無理は禁物じゃん
After all, I want you to be energetic, even if overdoing it is forbidden.
野菜室の我がまま者だな どっちどっちどっち
You're such a selfish vegetable drawer, which is it?
ちゃんと言葉で伝えたいな でもちょっと気づいてほしいな
I want to tell you in words, but I also want you to notice.
心臓から鼓動だな どっちどっちどっち
A heartbeat from my heart, which is it?
かんぜん beep beep beep
Completely beep beep beep...
ぜんぜん beep beep beep
Constantly beep beep beep...
君も同じになりなさい 顔を縦に振らせ
You should become the same, make your head nod up and down.
染まれ一切合切 その思いに
Be completely dyed in those feelings.
全部言っちゃえばだって なんか苦しそうじゃん
If you just tell me everything, 'cause you look kind of in pain.
言っちゃえばだって それで済むんだね了解
If you just say it, it's all resolved!
笑えるようになるまで 隣にステイでずっと馬鹿な冗談
Staying by your side until you can smile, telling silly jokes all along.
覚悟して
Prepare yourself!
ooh ra-ta-ta, sweet appetite
fearless, all my makeup is done
don't worry it's my queendom
look at me, the face i wanted to see
a makeover indeed am i your type ? do you like it ? ah , darling
A makeover indeed. Am I your type? Do you like it? Ah, darling
ooh ra-ta-ta, sweet appetite
come closer , now it's complete
Come closer, now it's complete
do you hear my heartbeat ?
Do you hear my heartbeat?
so far so good , you're setting the mood right but this is only going to drive me crazy
So far so good, you're setting the mood right, but this is only going to drive me crazy
are you embarrassed right now ? or blushing somehow ?
Are you embarrassed right now? Or blushing somehow?
but i am guessing it is the same for you and me look here , don't blink and tell me what you think
But I am guessing it is the same for you and me. Look here, don't blink and tell me what you think.
well , we both know the answer now , wouldn't you agree ?
Well, we both know the answer now, wouldn't you agree?
( fill my appetite ) what should i do
(Fill my appetite) What should I do?
i hope you don't find out the things i'm shy about
( fill my appetite ) what should i do
(Fill my appetite) What should I do?
my head is still spinning , the verge of exploding
My head is still spinning, on the verge of exploding
i'm only asking for another chance , ah
I'm only asking for another chance, ah
plan b , i'll get closer this time
Plan B, I'll get closer this time
next shot better be the bull's eye
new appeal , a sweet and spicy reveal
New appeal, a sweet and spicy reveal
my looks talk the talk but now my heart is still naked , ah , help me
My looks talk the talk, but now my heart is still naked, ah, help me
ooh ra-ta-ta, sweet appetite
i've got the tactics i need
uh ra-ta-ta sweet appetite
fearless, all my makeup is done
don't worry it's my queendom
look at me, the face i wanted to see
a makeover indeed
am i your type? do you like it? ah, darling
uh ra-ta-ta sweet appetite
come closer, now it's complete
do you hear my heartbeat?
so far so good, you're setting the mood right,
but this is only going to drive me crazy
are you embarrassed right now?
or blushing somehow?
but i am guessing it is the same for you and me
look here, don't blink
and tell me what you think
well we both know the answer now, wouldn't you agree?
fill my appetite
what should i do ...
What should I do...
i hope you don't find out the things i'm shy about
fill my appetite
what should i do ...
What should I do...
my head is still spinning, the verge of exploding
i'm only asking for another chance uh
plan b i'll get closer this time
next shot better be the bull's eye
new appeal, a sweet and spicy reveal
my looks talk the talk, but now my heart is still naked ...
My looks talk the talk, but now my heart is still naked...
ah, help me
uh ra-ta-ta sweet appetite
i've got the tactics i need
"patience" is just not for me
no, wait, stop now
god what was i thinking?
cause this is only driving me to full on panic!
心 寄せ 僅 か 歌う
Kokoro yose wazuka utau
花 の 根 に なりたい
Hana no ne ni naritai
色づく その 前 より
Irodzuku sono mae yori
しか と 地 に 立ち たい
Shikato chi ni tachi tai
口火 を 芽吹かせる
Kuchibi o mebukaseru
遣らずの雨が降ろうと
Yaranai no ame ga kudoro to
惰性 に 時間 を 齮ぐ こと なく
Dasei ni jikan o tsugumu koto naku
万屋の声を灯せば
Yoroza no koe o tomoseba
油煙 も 在りし 日 の 記録 に できる から
Abura kemu mo arashi hi no kiroku ni dekiru kara
涙云に一筋の風が吹く
Namida gumo ni hito suji no kaze ga fuku
桜は散らなければ愛されないと
Sakura wa saranakereba aisarenai to
光らぬ羽虫に夏なしと比べられるが
Hikaranu hane mushi ni nashi to kuraberareru ga
竹をかち割るくらいに身を切るくらいに塩を打つ
Take o kachiwaru kurai ni mi o kiru kurai ni shio o utsu
有明の先で
Arima ake no saki de
心寄せ僅か歌う
Kokoro yose wazuka utau
常しえに遥か忍ぶ
Joshige ni haruka shinobu
一途の一滴を垂らし続ける清水の如く
Ittou no ichiteki o tarashitsuzukeru seisui no gotoku
心寄せ僅か歌う
Kokoro yose wazuka utau
常しえに遥か忍ぶ
Joshige ni haruka shinobu
金色の髪が靡く
Kin-iro no kami ga namimeku
上がっちゃえちゃっけじらせ行こ
Agatsai chakeshi dase iko
さらばばば雲は組みつけて
Saraba ba ba kumowa kumitsukete
さわもるちょっはみ出して行こ
Sawa moru chotto hamidashite iko
さらばばばいつの日とかうんで行け勢い
Saraba ba ba itsu no hi to kaunden ikesei
きっと笑かしたいだい
Kitto warakashi tai dai
なんだったららったら全部忘れたよ
Nandattara rakutara zenbu wasureta yo
Say, ho!
もっと僕になるんだ
Motto boku ni naru n da
間違ったららったらなんて風流だもん
Machigattara rakutara nante kachoufuugetsu da mon
なんだったららったら全部忘れたよ
Nandattara rakutara zenbu wasureta yo
やる気でなくってのすたのすたむーどおっけー
Yaru ki denakutte nosuta nosuta muudo okkē
追い越し追い越されても大丈夫
Oikoshi oikosa rete mo daijoubu
諦めない言葉がきっと大正解
Akiramenai kotoba ga kitto daisankai
疲れたらちょっと休みなよ
Tsukaretara chotto yasumina yo
Say, ho!
不安になるのは君が君に期待してるのそそ所おこなう
Fuan ni naru no wa kimi ga kimi ni kitai shiteru no sososho okonau
そわくもなるのはそれは僕も一緒なんだよ
Sowaku naru no wa sore wa boku mo issho nan da yo
また行きたい回っちゃいたい走っていこ
Mata ikitai mawatchaitai hashiratte iko
さらばばばでさよぴあららせ
Saraba ba ba de sayo pi a rase
さわもるちょっおびのんでいこ
Samu wa mou chotto obi nonde iko
さらばばばフォナイトで笑うためぜぇ
Saraba ba ba for night de warau tame zē
きっと笑かしたいだい
Kitto warakashi tai dai
なんだったららったら全部忘れたよ
Nandattara rakutara zenbu wasureta yo
Say, ho!
もっと僕になるんだ
Motto boku ni naru n da
間違ったららったらなんて風流だもん
Machigattara rakutara nante kachoufuugetsu da mon
なんだったららったら全部忘れたよ
Nandattara rakutara zenbu wasureta yo
やる気でなくってのすたのすたむーどおっけー
Yaru ki denakutte nosuta nosuta muudo okkē
追い越し追い越されても大丈夫
Oikoshi oikosa rete mo daijoubu
諦めない言葉がきっと大正解
Akiramenai kotoba ga kitto daisankai
疲れたらちょっと休みなよ
Tsukaretara chotto yasumina yo
Say, ho!
不安になるのは君が君に期待してるのそそ所おこなう
Fuan ni naru no wa kimi ga kimi ni kitai shiteru no sososho okonau
そわくもなるのはそれは僕も一緒なんだよ
Sowaku naru no wa sore wa boku mo issho nan da yo
また行きたい回っちゃいたい走っていこ
Mata ikitai mawatchaitai hashiratte iko
さらばばばでさよぴあららせ
Saraba ba ba de sayo pi a rase
さわもるちょっおびのんでいこ
Samu wa mou chotto obi nonde iko
さらばばばフォナイトで笑うためぜぇ
Saraba ba ba for night de warau tame zē
きっと笑かしたいだい
Kitto warakashi tai dai
見乱堂のこんにちはでござる！
Miirado no konnichiwa de gozaru!
いろはでござる！
Iroha is here!
皆のヤッホーだって！
Everyone's saying "Yaho"!
うわ、すごい！うわ！うわ！出てる出てる！ありがとう！
Wow, amazing! Woah! Woah! They're coming out! Thank you!
ちょっと、すごいいっぱい動いてね、
I've been moving around so much,
ちょっとヘトヘトなところあるんですけども、
I'm getting a little exhausted, but...
風間の夢物語どうでしたかー！
How was Kazama's Dream Tale?!
うわあすごい！はーい！ありがとうございます！
Wow, amazing! Yay! Thank you very much!
憧れのね、この大きなステージに立つことができました！
I was able to stand on this big stage I've dreamed of!
みんなに会えて嬉しいでござる！
I'm so happy to see you all!
1人でのね、MCということですごく緊張しているんですけど
Since this is my first time doing an MC all by myself, I'm really nervous, but...
せっかく来たのでね、やっぱやってみたいことが風間あるんですけど、
Since I'm finally here, there's something I've been wanting to try—
皆の付き合ってくれますかー！
will you all go along with me?!
やったー！ありがとう！
Yay! Thank you!
じゃあみんなね、風間の決め台詞分かってると思うんですけど、ノットほにゃらら、イエスほにゃららをおね、
Now, I think everyone knows my catchphrase: "Not [blank], Yes [blank]"!
みんなで一緒にやりたいなと思うので風間のあとに続いてください！行くぞー！
I want us all to do it together, so please repeat after me! Here we go!
ノットー！
Not—!
イエスー！
Yes—!
うわあ、でござる！ありがとう！
Woah, de gozaru! Thank you!
わすごい！でも本当にね、こんな大きいステージを立ててびっくりしたんだけど、コメント欄のみんなも見えてますよ！
Wow, amazing! But really, I was so surprised to be on such a big stage, and I can see everyone in the comment section too!
見てるぞ！ジャキジャキにに、ありがとう！
I'm watching you! Sharp and bright, thank you!
で、さっきMio先輩と小雨ちゃんがね、どうやらコールアンドレスポンスなるものをやったんで風間もやってみたんですが、
And earlier, Mio-senpai and Koe-chan did some call-and-response thing, so I wanted to try it too,
せっかく来たからね、もっともっと遊んでいきたいななんて思っておりまして
and since I'm here, I want to have even more fun...
みんな、風間の色はは何色ですか？
Everyone, what color is Kazama's color?
うわ、すごい！色が、色がついてる！
Wow, amazing! The colors, the colors are on!
じゃあそのペンライトでウェーブやっていきたいと思います！
Now let's do a wave with those penlights!
こっちの方から行くよー！
Starting from this side!
行きます！せーの、うわー！
Here we go! Ready, go—woah!
え、すごい！めっちゃ綺麗！みんなのありがとう！
Whoa, amazing! So pretty! Thank you everyone!
はい、ここから先もね、ホロライブのステージまだまだ続いていきます！
Yes, from here on too, the Hololive stage will continue!
素敵な楽曲、そしてダンスがどんどん続いていくのでお楽しみに！
Wonderful music and dances will keep coming, so look forward to it!
そして何やらここから先はちょっと違った世界観にと、いうことで風間もどうなるかドキドキなんですが、
And from here on, it has a slightly different world view, so I'm nervous to see how it'll turn out,
一緒にこの後も楽しみましょうね！
but let's enjoy the rest together!
もっと、本当はおしゃべりしたいけど風間もね、次にいかなきゃいけないんで
I'd really love to talk more, but I have to move on to the next thing,
みんなとの締めのご挨拶わかっているでござりような！
so you know what our concluding greeting is, right?!
あ、し、しまった！
Ah, o-oh no!
風間が一個大事なこと忘れた。
I forgot one important thing.
許して。YouTubeの、皆のの、
Forgive me. YouTube, everyone's...
YouTubeでの皆ののこちらね、配信が無料パートここまでとなっております！
The free broadcasted part on YouTube ends right here!
寂しい！寂しいけど！
So lonely! It's lonely, but!
まだまだね、一緒に盛り上がりたい皆のは概要欄からここここここ、ぜひね、配信サイトへチケット買いに来てくださいねー！
For those of you who want to get hyped together, from the description box right here, please come buy tickets to the streaming site!
というわけで今度こそ締め直しますよ！
So without further ado, let's do the concluding greeting properly this time!
皆のの決め台詞準備はいいでござるか？
Are you all ready for our catchphrase?
それでは！せーの！広がり、
Ready, set! Expanding,
ホロライブ！
Hololive!
無料パートは終了いたしました！ご視聴ありがとうございました！
[Free broadcast ended! Thank you for watching!]
無料パートは終了いたしました！
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free part has ended!
Thank you for watching!
無料パートは終了いたしました！ ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free part has ended! Thank you for watching!